https://www.remmeer.com/privacy-security/

Home / Privacy & Security
We value your privacy and security and will not do any thing to jeopardize your trust. We work diligently to guard your privacy and to protect your security so that you can relax and enjoy your visit. A detailed explanation of our Privacy & Security notice is displayed below.
Non-personal Information
Like many other web sites, we collect non-personal information to make your visit more satisfying. Non-personal information is usually associated with a particular computer or IP address but not with a particular person.
The anonymous information that is gathered is unobtrusively collected through the use of “cookies.” A cookie is a small bit of data that is sent to your browser and stored on your computer’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Each time you access our web site, our server finds the relevant cookie on your computer. The information is used to help us identify such things as pages viewed and product searches in an effort to make our site more rewarding to our visitors. No personal data is obtained through this tracking beyond the IP address of the visitor.
You may set your browser to block cookies and still view our site. However, you will not be able to make a purchase since cookies are required to identify the items you have placed in your shopping cart.
If you are experiencing difficulty with the functionality of our site, it may be due to your computer not being set to accept cookies. lease refer to your browser’s internet option settings for information on how to enable your browser to accept cookies.
Personally Identifiable Information
We also collect personally identifiable information that you provide us. Personally identifiable information consists of information that is unique to you. This information includes your name, billing address, shipping address, telephone number and email address. This information is only required if you would like to set up an account or make a purchase. The personal information is used to verify your credit card information, notify you of your order’s status and to ship your order.
Although your credit card information is required during the checkout process, it is only used to process the transaction. Your credit card information is not retained as part of your account information. We do not store credit card information.
Updating Account Information
You always have the option to access your account to ensure that the information you have supplied is correct. In addition, you have the option of removing any information from your account that you wish to keep private. However, please note that removing certain information may make it impossible for us to provide the service or products you have requested. We recommend that you contact us first to discuss which information you may safely remove without interrupting service.
SSL Encryption
The submission of all account information and the processing of credit card transactions are performed on a secure web server while using 256 bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption software. This state-of-the-art security protocol encrypts your information to ensure that any sensitive information that is sent by you to us via the Internet is protected from unauthorized interception.
SSL technology is automatically activated before you log onto your account and begin entering your credit card information. (When SSL is enabled, most browsers will display a “padlock” symbol at the bottom of the screen. A secure server location is indicated by the “https://” URL prefix in your browser’s address line. The “s” in the prefix indicates that that web page is secure.)
Internal Safeguards
We employ firewall protection to prevent unauthorized access to your account information. In addition, passwords are required in order to gain access to your account information, which included your name, address, telephone number and email address. (Once again, Remmeer.com does not store credit card information.)
All of our employees are prohibited from disclosing any customer information to any individuals or entities that are not directly associated with the processing and fulfillment of an order. Only those employees that have a need-to-know basis can access your information. When an employee is terminated or is no longer with the company, we change the access codes that the employee used to access any customer accounts. Additionally, technicians under our direction may have access to your information in order to conduct routine checks on the integrity of our system and in order to perform necessary maintenance work.
In order to process your credit card we have to consult with an outside credit card processing company. The processing company is regulated by the banking industry and must meet certain security requirements in order to be in business. The processing company will have access to your credit card information, billing address, name, and telephone number. The processing company will communicate with the issuing bank of your credit card in order to get final approval to charge your credit card for the product or services we are providing for you.
Third-Party Disclosures
We will never sell, rent or give your personal information, including your email address, to any third party (except when necessary to complete a purchase that you have requested or when required to do so by law).
Legally-Obligated Disclosures
We may disclose your personally identifiable information if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so in order to comply with applicable law, a subpoena, or other legal process. We may also disclose personally identifiable information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Conditions of Use or to protect the safety of our users and the general public.
Spam
We do not send unsolicited emails. Your contact information will only be used to contact you about your order, if necessary. We will not use your email to send you periodic promotional notices unless you specifically request us to do so. Even then, you may request, at any time, to be removed from our mailing list.
Children
The content on our website is intended for general audiences. While visitors of all ages are encouraged to visit our site, we do not permit children under the age of 18 to purchase products. If you are under the age of 18, please ask your parent or guardian for assistance.
Third-Party Sites
Our site may contain hyperlinks to other websites. We have no control over the policies of third-party sites. The policies of these sites may vary. Please consult the individual sites to determine their policies.
Notice of Policy Changes
We reserve the right to change our Privacy & Security Notice at any time.
